so
moved to Las Vegas
10 years ago from New Jersey the Garden
State don't you love that the Garden
State apparently someone's neglected to
attend this Garden for the past 50-60
years
now the brown and crumbly state
says still on those special license
plates
folks back East can't believe I live in
Las Vegas somebody has to live there you
know
they really can't believe I live in the
desert that's like ooh that blows their
mind that's exotic they don't know
anything about the desert so you can
tell them anything when they ask Dopey
questions about it
oh I hear it's hot there yeah I bet it's
a dry heat oh yeah
oh I hear it rains a lot too yeah but
it's a dry rain
well do you gamble a lot more
uh no
but I gamble in different ways
for instance I now buy meat at the
dollar store
they got some crazy stuff with the dogs
so the other day I bought a Yankee
Candle I brought it home I lit it
smelled like Reggie Jackson
I got doggy ice cream ice cream for dogs
this is a dumb idea I had nothing to do
with it tastes terrible by the way
cream for dogs save your money
they already have ice cream for dogs
it's called ice cream
it's good enough for me it's good enough
for the dog it's not like he's got a
waistline to worry about he's not even
wearing pants
at least not as often I'd like him too
you know there's a chain of dollar
stores called Dollar General which also
sounds like a really terrible Hospital
Dollar General
you get a CAT scan there they use a real
cat
pulled into a place called Family Dollar
it's a big old ugly family in the
parking lot having an argument I
couldn't help but listen in
turns out not one of them remembered to
bring the Family Dollar
foreign
it's a Dollar Store near my house called
Everything's a Dollar so one day I
walked in
put a dollar down on the counter back
the truck up to the front
loaded everything in
I am now the proud owner of a truckload
of crap from China
I think it'll start my own dollar store
now I'm taking a call to crap from China
or maybe each thing's a dollar
paid attention in English class
they got a strange idea what constitutes
entertainment in Las Vegas I'll tell you
that much
got a lot of those Escape rooms now
anybody do the escape room say yeah
in case you don't know what an escape
room is
this room where they lock in a room with
a bunch of strangers you all got to get
together and figure out how to get out
anybody who thinks this is entertaining
has never done jury duty
Las Vegas is now home to the world's
tallest ferris wheel they don't call the
first wheel they call it observation
wheel who named that that's not fun
55 stories tall just what you want the
middle of the Nevada desert you want to
be 550 feet closer to the Sun
30 minutes for one complete rotation
they call it the High Roller I like to
call it the rotisserie
50 bucks I feel like
see this a lot walking around the
casinos you see a gorgeous girl
accompanied by her two somewhat less
gorgeous girlfriends
I like to call that change for a 20.
it's a ten and two fives
it's a wedding party it's a ten of five
and five ones
apparently the schools in Las Vegas are
terrible but I don't own a home I don't
pay taxes I don't have any kids so I
don't care
I don't know if it's true or not I will
say this there's an elementary school
near where I live that has student
parking
[Music]
something's going horribly wrong
apparently it's tough to teach math
say this because I went to the grocery
store the other day out front with a
bunch of these big ceramic pots one sign
one sign all it says is 50 off
so I walk in I ask the young lady I said
what's the regular price of these
ceramic pots she looks at me and she
says
a hundred percent
oh I'm the dumb one
I'm Brian McKim thank you for watching
my dry bar comedy special don't forget
to download the dry bar comedy app onto
your smartphone and don't forget to use
the promo code Brian McKim that's Brian
McKim m-c-k-i-m
thank you